Guide to the Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
21-24-1975
Cornell University.Cooperative Extension.
67.4 Cubic Feet.
Printed Materials, Reports, Photographs, Videotapes
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cooperative Extension Administration files regarding county extension associations; Cornell departments including Agricultural Economics, Agricultural Engineering, Agronomy, Animal Science, Botany, Conservation, Entomology, Food Science, Plant Breeding and Biometry, Rural Sociology, Communication Arts, and Buildings and Grounds; committees and special projects; community resource development; project summaries, 1914-1965; some annual summaries of county farm bureaus and home bureaus. Also, miscellaneous files on dairy herd improvement, 1919; farm management, 1917-1918; National Board of Farm Organizations, 1919; New York State Dept. of Health; New York State Grange, 1918-1919; agricultural conservation, 1936; Farm and Home Week, 1930-1942; farm debt adjustment and debt reconciliation, 1934; farm forestry program, 1939; Farm Bureau Federation, 1938 and 1940; rural electrification program, 1936-1942; rural housing, 1946-1947; and World War II activities. Files of Lincoln Kelsey, primarily relating to Cornell United Religious work and to the Christian Rural Fellowship movement; radio speech scripts, 1932-1941; and negotiations about the Bartlett Club, 1947. Also, Annual Reports (1944-1960); "On the Extension Line" (1968-1992); and "Perspectives" (1992), and two student papers on Extension written by Lucinda Noble (1959).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Cooperative Extension Administration files regarding county extension associations; Cornell departments including Agricultural Economics, Agricultural Engineering, Agronomy, Animal Science, Botany, Conservation, Entomology, Food Science, Plant Breeding and Biometry, Rural Sociology, Communication Arts, and Buildings and Grounds; committees and special projects; community resource development; project summaries, 1914-1965; some annual summaries of county farm bureaus and home bureaus. Also, miscellaneous files on dairy herd improvement, 1919; farm management, 1917-1918; National Board of Farm Organizations, 1919; New York State Dept. of Health; New York State Grange, 1918-1919; agricultural conservation, 1936; Farm and Home Week, 1930-1942; farm debt adjustment and debt reconciliation, 1934; farm forestry program, 1939; Farm Bureau Federation, 1938 and 1940; rural electrification program, 1936-1942; rural housing, 1946-1947; and World War II activities. Files of Lincoln Kelsey, primarily relating to Cornell United Religious work and to the Christian Rural Fellowship movement; radio speech scripts, 1932-1941; and negotiations about the Bartlett Club, 1947. Also, Annual Reports (1944-1960); "On the Extension Line" (1968-1992); and "Perspectives" (1992), and two student papers on Extension written by Lucinda Noble (1959).
Financial records regarding the publication of the Bulletin and Experiment Station Memoir, published by Cooperative Extension for the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station at Ithaca. Includes material on Hurricane Agnes and the Flood of 1972; Extension Faculty Resources material; and records relating to the New York State Association of Extension Home Economists, and the American Home Economics Association.
Eleven cards, 5/17/1915-8/17/1927, published by Cooperative Agricultural Extension Work in cooperation with the New York State Food Supply Commission. These cards contain helpful information regarding preparation and preservation of foods.
Includes publications and videotapes of various extension programs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Kelsey, Lincoln David, 1894-; American Farm Bureau Federation.; American Home Economics Association.; Christian Rural Fellowship.; Cornell United Religious Work.; Cornell University.Dept. of Plant Breeding.; Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (U.S.); National Extension Homemakers Council (U.S.); New York (State).Dept. of Health.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.; New York State Association of Extension Home Economists.; New York State College of Agriculture--Buildings.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Agricultural Economics.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Agricultural Engineering.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Agronomy.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Animal Science.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Botany.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Conservation.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Entomology.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Food Science.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Social Organization.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Communication Arts.
Titles:
On the Extension line.; Perspectives.
Subjects:
Agricultural extension work--New York (State); Rural development projects--New York (State); Agriculture--New York (State)--Finance.; Forestry projects--New York (State); Agricultural conservation--New York (State); Rural electrification--New York (State); Rural extension--New York (State); Home demonstration work--United States.; Home economics extension work--United States.; Housing, Rural--New York (State); Dairy cattle--New York (State)--Breeding.; Hurricane Agnes, 1972.
Form and Genre Terms:
Videotapes.; Audiotapes.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Additional material and digital versions can be found online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/1440
RELATED MATERIAL
See also collections #23-2-749, New York State College of Home Economics records; #23-2-2817, New York State College of Human Ecology records; #21-24-692, 4-H Club records; #21-24-3292, Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program records; #29-4-2733 Division of Nutritional Sciences Cooperative Extension Nutrition Program records; and #29-1-3247, Division of Nutritional Sciences records for related material.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Subject Files
Series II. Awards and Biographical Material
Series III. Publications
Cornell Publications
External Publications
Papers, Articles and Flyers
Cooperative Extension Notes
Discussion Papers
On the Extension Line (OTEL) Perspectives
Series IV. Initiatives, Projects, Plans, Reports,
Community Resource Development Narrative Reports
Series V. DVDs, Videotapes and Audiotapes
Series VI. Conferences, Inservice Programs, Resource Manuals
Series VII. Correspondence
Series VIII. Associations (County, State, National)- Historical Material
Series IX. Photographs and Slides
Series X. Financial Records and Compliance Reviews
Fiscal Year Plan of Work
Series XI. Committees, Councils, Programs
Advisory Council
Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP)
East Harlem Nutrition Education Program
Extension Service Summer School Program
Extension Study Committee
National Extension Homemakers Council
Potato Committee
Resilient Communities Program
4-H
Various other Committees and Programs
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Subject Files
  - General
  - Extension Administration Files, 1950-1963 (Box 3)
    - Agriculture Economics Department (Box 3)
      Census, Credit, Farm Management, Marketing, Marketing Projects, Regional Marketing Committees, Agriculture Policy
    - Agricultural Engineering Department- Irrigation (Box 3)
    - Agronomy Department-Soil Testing, Sugar Beets (Box 3)
    - Animal Science Department-Animal Husbandry (Box 3)
    - Botany (Box 3)
    - Conservation Department-Wood Products Utilization (Box 3)
    - Entomology Department-Pesticides and Spray Residues (Box 3)
    - Food Science Department (Box 3)
    - Plant Breeding and Biometrics Department (Box 3)
    - Rural Sociology Department-Population and Census (Box 3)
    - Buildings and Grounds (Box 3)
      Federal Building Space, Roberts Hall Space, State Building Space
    - Communication Arts Department (Box 3)
      TV Film Center, Correspondence Courses, Direct Mail, Press and Mail, Public Relations, Public Speaking, Role Playing, Television, Visual Aids, Publications, County Extension Service Association Publications, Current Episodes, Distribution, Public Relations Leaflets
  - Annual Extension Project Summaries, 1914-1945 (Box 5)
    Includes the plan for each funded project with budget, staff assigned and planned activities
  - Annual Extension Project Summaries (continued), 1945-1965 (Box 6)
    In Front
  - Annual Summaries of County Farm Bureaus, 1916-1956 (Box 6)
    In Back, Includes County Home Bureaus for some years, and some years missing from 1926-1956.
  - Cooperative Extension Administration: Miscellaneous Information, 1917-1942 (Box 7)
    The materials in this box were sorted from files found on the fourth floor of Roberts Hall.
    - Cornell University Religious Works (CURW)- minutes of meetings, pamphlets, correspondence, reports, 1936-1943 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
    - Cornell Missionary School Material, 1933-1943 (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
    - New York Christian Rural Fellowship Bulletin, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - General Trends and Rural Situation -background information of interest to rural ministers, 1929-1937 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Christian Rural Fellowship - including information about Lisle Conference, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Christian Rural Fellowship Bulletin, 1935-1941 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Christian Rural Fellowship Bulletin, 1937-1943 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Near East Foundation, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Near East Foundation Program Committee, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Near East Relief, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Near East Foundation - Correspondence, 1943-1948 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Extension's Part in Soil Conservation, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Bartlett Carry Club, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Radio Talks, 1931-1941 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Diary Herd Improvement, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Farm Management, 1917-1918 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Home Bureau Membership, 1918-1942 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Milk Show - New York City, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence/ Extension Administration, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 22-24)
    - National Board of Farm Organizations, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - New York State Department of Health, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - New York State Grange, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Nitrate of Soda Program, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - State Fair, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Victory Special, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - War Effects, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Extension Work in New York State- Memos, correspondence, including information about the Wattmobile, 1938-1942 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Extension Teaching 103 Class Material, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Extension Teaching 103 Class Material, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Digest of Federal Programs as related to the Extension Service in New York State, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Cooperative Extension Administration: Miscellaneous Information, 1930-1942 (Box 8)
    - Agriculture Conservation, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Agricultural Land Use, 1938-1941 (Box 8, Folder 2-4)
    - Conference Board of Farm Organizations, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Farm and Home Week, 1930-1942 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
    - Farm Debt Adjustment and Debt Reconciliation, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Farm Forestry Program, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Flood Control Clippings, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Flood and Follow Up, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
    - Farm Bureau Federation-History of American Farm Bureau, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Farm Bureau Federation, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Rural Electrification Program, 1936-1942 (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
    - Rural Housing, 1936-1947 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Rural Rehabilitation, 1935-1939 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Soil Conservation, 1936-1940 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Wartime: gasoline, tires, etc., 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - History of Agricultural Extension Work in the United States-Dr. A.C. True, 1940 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Radio Broadcasting by County Extension Agents and letters from L.R. Simons and replies from Agents, 1940-1957 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Coordination of Agricultural Programs for Economy and Efficiency-prepared by L.R. Simons, 1943-1945 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Cooperative Extension Books: Department of Extension Studies (Box 11)
    - Special Reports 1-29 (2 volumes)
    - Extension Study 1-19 (3 volumes)
    - Miscellaneous Reports (1 volume)
    - Reports 1-12 (1 volume)
      Evaluation Study of Farm and Home Management Program in New York State
    - Farm Labor-War Administration, 1944 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Farm and Home Special Demonstration Train, 1946 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - New York State Commission Against Discrimination, 1949-1950 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Xandria-Charles S. Brown Estate on Oneida Lake (Shackelton's Point, New York), 1949-1955 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Myers, W.I.-Talks, 1950-1959 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Memo from Charles Brannan to Murry Lincoln concerning Saturday Evening Post article "Wow! Did Truman Ever Fool the Farmers", 1952 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Knapp, Seaman A.-correspondence, memos, 1952-1953 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - 50th Anniversary-New York State College of Agriculture, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Northern New York-Regional Research Laboratory, 1954-1960 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Bond, M.C.-Talks, 1954-1961 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - "A Balanced United States Agriculture in 1965"-National Planning Association, 1956 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - 1912 Farm and Home Special - M.F. Barrus, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Liberty Hyde Bailey Centennial Celebration, 1957-1958 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Chemical Insecticide Corporation, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Milk-Antibiotics and Pesticides, 1957-1960 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - History of Cornell University-Excerpts from Cornell Registers, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Appraisal of Services by the Federal Extension Service, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Census of Agriculture, 1959-1961 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Cooperative Extension: Extension Advisory Council Meeting Information, 1970-1985 (Box 12)
    - Statistical Information, 1945-1969
    - Memorandum of Agreement Correspondence, 1960-1969
    - Cornell Extension Club Information, 1967-1974
    - Current Episodes, New York State Extension Service Newsletter, 1946-1965
    - The Extender Newsletter, 1988-03, 1988-10, 1988-11 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Early Sabbatic and Leaves Correspondence, 1930-1967
    - Early New York City Material, 1918-1919
    - Correspondence relating to Ruby Green Smith, F.W. Howe Martha Van Rensselaer, A.R. Mann, and home demonstration agents, 1918-1942
    - Cornell OEO Project: An Exploration in Urban Extension Activity (Office of Economic Opportunity)
    - Cornell OEO Project:Supplementary Reports 1-5, 1971
  - Inventory for the records of the New York State Cooperative Extension Services (Box 40)
    Contains information dealing with various topics used in Home Demonstrations in different countries in the 1950's. The records were found in Helen Bayer's office.
    - Department of Child Development and Family Relationships - records concerning adolescence, 1950-1959 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
    - Home Demonstration Extension Specialists, Trip Report Forms, 1959-1961 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Same as Above, 1957-1959 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Topic: Building Personality - Living Together in the family (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
    - Topic: A Child 4-6 Starting School (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Topic: A Child and His Friends, 1950-1959 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Topic: The Child From 6-12 (Box 40, Folder 9-10)
    - Children Together in the Family (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Topic: Getting Along with Others (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Healthy Personality (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Family and Community (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Getting Along with Others and Helping Children Understand Sex (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Helping Young People for marriage (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Understanding Children 6-12 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Living Together in the Family (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Understanding Ourselves and Others (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - 4-H Curriculum by Paula Eisner (Box 40, Folder 20)
      Re: Children and How They Learn (It includes some examples of completed work and several comments on curriculum)
  - Extension Positions-Memos, 1965-1968 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Cooperative Extension - Studies and Research, 1951-1952 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Cooperative Extension - Reorganization, 1964-1965 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Cooperative Extension - Reorganization of County Extension Organizations, 1965-1966 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Cooperative Extension - New York State Organizational Guide, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Cooperative Extension - New York State Organizational Guide, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Cooperative Extension - Home Demonstration Units: the role they play, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Special Communication System- An Experimental System for Communication with Hard-To-Reach People (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - On Strong Link: A manual prepared by Department of Community Service Education, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - 4-H program, 1980-1989 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Cooperative Extension- Scope and Priorities: guidelines for program direction, 1970-1975 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Cooperative Extension- E.N.E.P. Guides for Aides (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Limited Resources Farm Management Program, Chenango County- Final Report by Gerald LeClar, 1979-07 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - The Learning Needs and Interests of Adult Blue Collar Factory Workers by Peter Botsman (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Maximizing Volunteers in Program Delivery: done in pilot counties, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Good Nutrition: An Investment in Your Family's Future by Ardyth Gillespie, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Good Nutrition: An Investment in Your Family's Future- Users Guide by Ardyth Gillespie, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Good Nutrition: The Nutrient Guide - by Ardyth Gillespie, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 31A)
  - Reports: (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Home Economics: the Third Generation A Focus for the 80's
    - Trends- A Resource to Aid in Program Development
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Work in Metropolitan Areas, 1986
    - Facts about Cooperative Extension New York State, 1976, 1981, 1986
  - Cooperative Extension Administration, 1990-1999 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Perspectives for the 70's: Cooperative Extension- Program Scope and Priorities, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Family Day Care Program- Cooperative Extension, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Family Day Care Program Scrapbook, 1973-1977 (Box 63)
  - Epsilon Sigma Phi Awards, 1965-1979 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Flood- Hurricane Agnes, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Flood- Hurricane Agnes, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Flood- Hurricane Agnes, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Flood- Hurricane Agnes, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Flood- Hurricane Agnes: Articles, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Flood- Hurricane Agnes: Extension Information, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Aid to Flooded Families, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    Summer
  - Aid to Flooded Families, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Flood Material- County Developments, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Flood- How Cooperative Extension Assisted, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Flood- How Cooperative Extension Assisted, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Disaster Handbook for Extension Agents, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Staff- "A Task Force Approach to Better Use of Staff Resources in Counties in New York" submitted by Natalie Crowe, 1969-06 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Staffing Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1980-1989 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Accountability Programs- 1983 and 1992 "Six Initiatives", 1983, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - PROMAS- Software, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Steps in Program Evaluation, 1980-1989 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - National Association of Extension Home Economics (NAEHE) History, 1933-1975 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Home Demonstration- "Trends Likely to Affect Home Demonstration Work in New York State", Olaf Larson and USDA booklet about Home Demonstration, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Extension Workers Manual for Selecting and Using Local Volunteer Leaders- (1980) Organization and Administration of the New York State Cooperative Extension Service, 1958-1959 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - "Cooperative Extension in New York State- A Management Survey" by Robert Kerker, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1995-2001 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Disaster Preparedness and Response, 1998-2001 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Diversity-Memos, Reports, Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Diversity-Memos, Correspondence, 1991-2001 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Diversity-Memos, Reports, Correspondence, 1994-1999 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Diversity-Memos, Reports, Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Diversity-Memos, Reports, Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Diversity-Change Agent States for Diversity, 1998-2000 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Diversity-Change Agent States for Diversity, 2000-2002 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Empire Farm Days, 1986-2000 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Equal Opportunity Policy Statement, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Onion-Articles and Correspondence, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - Outreach, 1992-1998 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Michigan State/Cornell Cooperative Extension Visit, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Second Tuesday, 1993-2001 (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - Extension Administration and Organization
  - New York State College Agricultural Council-Strucure and Purpose-Statement of H.E. Babcock at Board of Trustees Meeting, 1940-08-14 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station-County Agricultural Agents Relationship to Programs, 1945 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Number of Cooperative Extension Personnel, 1949-1965 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Agents and the Association-Meeting of Senior Agents, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Role and Responsibilities of the Director's Representative, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Extension Administration Files regarding:, 1950-1963 (Box 2)
    Country Extension Service Associations. (Correspondence, etc., by county)
  - Public Service-Extension, 1963-1974 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Extension Administration-Ranking Job Descriptions, 1966-1971 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Organization of County Extension Staff, 1969-1975 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Extension Administration Goals, 1974-1994 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Extension-Organization, 1976-1992 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Professional Development Plan for Non-Professional Academics, 1979-1980 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Accountability and Evaluation Forms, 1982-1998 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Ad Hoc County Coordinators, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Staffing, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Capital District-Media/Marketing Specialist Position, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Regional Meetings- Cooperative Extension, 1980-1989 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Regional Meetings- Cooperative Extension, 1980-1989 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Program Staffing Plans-Regional Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Challenges Facing Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Budget Request, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - "Organizational Leadership During Periods of Decline in Not-For-Profit Educational Systems"-by Glenn Applebee, 1990-1999 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Extension Associates and Senior Extension Associates-Promotions, Information Handbook, Reports, Memos, 1992-2004 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Extension Administration-Organization Facts, 1994-1996 (Box 75, Folder 27)